

#### **PROFILE**

I live in the City of Buenos Aires, born on september 18, in 1986, I am currently in the Jobs search in the systems sector. I am currently and in testing them, My focus is dedicated to the parts of unit testing.

Why am I applying for systems, adn even more so for the testing área? Because I am aware that in this sector, thinking outside the box is required and havint a technical profile with experience in other áreas allows me to bring a differentes prespective when conducting tests.

#### CONTACT

MOVILE: +54 9 11-6837-0362 E-MAIL: <u>Jurquiza86@hotmail.com</u>

Repository: <a href="https://github.com/Jonat">https://github.com/Jonat</a> <a href="https://github.com/Jonat">hanUrquiza?tab=repositories</a>

#### Networks:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-urquiza-179a70119/

#### TOOLS:

- HTML5 (advance).
- CSS3 (advance).
- Bootstrap (middle).
- MySQL. (knowledge).
- JavaScript (knowledge).
- Python.(knowledge).
- ReactJS (knowledge).
- Java (knowledge).
- PHPmyadmin (knowledge).
- nodeJS(basic).
- Postman.(basic)

# JONATHAN JAVIER URQUIZA

# **EDUCATION**

Higher vocational training institute N° 4 (IFTS N° 4 technicality)

03/03/2023 - In progress

**Highe Technician in system Analisys** 

Codo a Codo 4.0

03/02/2023 - 25/06/2023

Testina QC Automatition.

CoderHouse

18/08/2022 - 19/01/2023

Web dev. Programing in javascript.

Tenchnical School N°30 "Dr. Norberto Piñero" (high school)

03/03/2012 - 12/12/2018

Development of proyet planning of different scales, administration and resource management.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Taller K&J Racing (electronic component test and diagnostic)

March 2017 - Janury 2021

- Analysis of electronic devices.
- Purchasing management.
- Customer support.
- Deivices repair.

# Repair, modificaction and mantenance (freelance).

March 2016 - Janury 2017

- Team management.
- Customer support.
- Resurce managment.
- Equipment management.
- Requirements analisys.

# **SOFT SKILS**

- Team work.
- Analitical and curious.
- Continuous improvement.
- English (middle level, speack and write).
- Agile metodology(scrum).

# **MANAGMENT TOOLS**

- Trello.
- SpiraPlan.
- Jira.